<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Austin, TX Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="TabItem1">Historic Sites</string>
    <string name="TabItem2">Outdoors Activities</string>
    <string name="TabItem3">Food</string>
    <string name="TabItem4">Music</string>
    <string name="Historic0">Capital Building</string>
    <string name="Historic0_Description">The Capitol Building was built in 1885. At the time of it’s construction, it was the seventh largest building in the world. It houses the Texas legislature and the Governor’s office.</string>
    <string name="Historic1">Driskill Hotel</string>
    <string name="Historic1_Description">The Driskill hotel was built in 1886. It is the oldest hotel still operating in Austin, Texas.	</string>
    <string name="Historic2">Susanna Dickinson Museum</string>
    <string name="Historic2_Description">The former house of Susanna Dickinson was built in 1869. Susanna Dickinson is famous as the sole survivor of the Alamo. The house now serves as a museum and houses artifacts that were former possessions of Susanna Dickinson.</string>
    <string name="Historic3">Austin Fire Museum</string>
    <string name="Historic3_Description">The Austin Fire Museum is located inside Central Fire Station No. 1 in downtown Austin. The museum features firefighting equipment from the 19th century to the 21st century. It is open Wednesday - Sunday 12p - 5p.</string>
    <string name="Historic4">Paramount Theatre</string>
    <string name="Historic4_Description">The Paramount Theatre is a live theatre and movie theatre that was built in 1915. It is listed in the National Register of Historic Places.</string>
    <string name="Outdoors0">Barton Springs</string>
    <string name="Outdoors0_Description">Barton Springs Pool is a great way to cool off during the summer months. The natural spring water here is averages around 70 degrees fahrenheit. </string>
    <string name="Outdoors1">Greenbelt</string>
    <string name="Outdoors1_Description">Hike, bike, swim, or rock climb at the Barton Creek Greenbelt. This park consists of miles of trail and quiet scenery.</string>
    <string name="Outdoors2">Mount Bonnell</string>
    <string name="Outdoors2_Description">Mt Bonnell is a 775 mount overlooking Lake Austin. It is one of the highest points in the Austin area and provides a scenic view of downtown.	</string>
    <string name="Outdoors3">Zilker Park</string>
    <string name="Outdoors3_Description">Zilker Park is located just south of downtown Austin. It lies between Barton Creek and the Colorado River. Zilker park offers picnicking areas and even has a botanical garden. This park is most famous as the site of the Austin City Limits festival in fall.</string>
    <string name="Outdoors4">McKinney Falls</string>
    <string name="Outdoors4_Description">McKinney Falls is a 744 acre state park located in south Austin. Situated between Onion Creek and Williamson Creek, It offers hiking and camping.</string>
    <string name="Outdoors5">Hamilton Pool</string>
    <string name="Outdoors5_Description">Hamilton Pool is a swimming hole located just outside of Austin in Dripping Springs, TX. It features a 50 foot waterfall and a bowl-shaped canyon. This destination now requires a reservation to visit.</string>
    <string name="Restaurants0">Casa Colombia</string>
    <string name="Restaurants0_Description">Casa Colombia is located in East Austin. It is a local favorite offering authentic Columbian fare.</string>
    <string name="Restaurants1">Franklin Barbecue</string>
    <string name="Restaurants1_Description">Franklin Barbecue is located in downtown Austin. This establishment put Central Texas barbecue on the map. It consistently is ranked among the top barbecue restaurants in Texas and nationally. Wait times for a table are often 3-5 hours.</string>
    <string name="Restaurants2">Salt and Time</string>
    <string name="Restaurants2_Description">Located on the Eastside of Austin, Salt and Time is primarily a butcher shop. During lunch and dinner hours, they serve some of the best burgers and sandwiches in Austin.	</string>
    <string name="Restaurants3">Kemuri Tatsu-ya</string>
    <string name="Restaurants3_Description">Kemuri Tatsu-ya is a fairly new restaurant created by the founders of beloved Ramen house Ramen Tatsu-ya. Kemuri Tatsu-ya offers Texas takes on a traditional Japanese Izakaya.</string>
    <string name="Restaurants4">Odd Duck</string>
    <string name="Restaurants4_Description">Odd Duck is an upscale New American style restaurant. Odd Duck follows a farm to table philosophy and offers a one of a kind experience.</string>
    <string name="Restaurants5">Torchy\'s Tacos</string>
    <string name="Restaurants5_Description">Beloved Austin chain for non-traditional tacos. Torchy’s tacos began life as a taco truck, but soon grew into a national brick-and-mortar chain.</string>
    <string name="Restaurants6">La Barbecue</string>
    <string name="Restaurants6_Description">La Barbecue is another beloved barbecue restaurant located on the Eastside of Austin. La Barbecue founder Leann Mueller comes from a pedigree of “Texas barbecue royalty.” This spot offers an alternative to Franklin barbecue with still long, but slightly shorter wait times.</string>
    <string name="LiveMusic0">Stubb\'s Bar B Q</string>
    <string name="LiveMusic0_Description">Stubb\’s Bar B Q is a restaurant and concert venue located in downtown Austin, TX. This is a larger outdoor venue (2,200 person capacity) that hosts many bigger names in the music industry.</string>
    <string name="LiveMusic1">Empire Garage</string>
    <string name="LiveMusic1_Description">Empire Control Room and Garage offers a more intimate environment to catch favorite local and national acts. The Control Room has become one of the premier spots for electronic music in Austin.</string>
    <string name="LiveMusic2">Emo\'s</string>
    <string name="LiveMusic2_Description">Emo\’s is a midsize concert venue located in South Austin. Locals know that shows at Emo’s have excellent sound quality. This venue typically caters to live performances featuring top notch performers.</string>
    <string name="LiveMusic3">Scoot Inn</string>
    <string name="LiveMusic3_Description">Founded in the 1800’s, Scoot Inn is one of the oldest music venues in Austin. Located downtown, it is an outdoor venue with a mid-sized capacity.</string>
    <string name="LiveMusic4">Mohawk</string>
    <string name="LiveMusic4_Description">The Mohawk is a mid-sized outdoor venue located in downtown Austin. This venue typically features indie rock acts. </string>
    <string name="LiveMusic5">Hole in the Wall</string>
    <string name="LiveMusic5_Description">Located near UT campus, Hole in the Wall is a legendary smaller venue. Playing this bar has been a right of passage for many now famous musicians.</string>
</resources>
